(Howard:)By her. Oh, look, I did it again.
MISSY: Well, that should do it.
- Thank you for coming by.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, buddy.
Buddy?
(Howard:)Sorry I'm late.
I'm working on a project...
(Howard:)...that may take me up
on the next space shuttle.
Well, how can you be late?
I wasn't expecting you at all.
(Howard:)Nobody ever expects me.
(Howard:)Sometimes you just look,
and bam, Howard Wolowitz.
- Sheldon, are you gonna introduce us?
- Oh, all right. This is Missy.
(Sheldon:)Missy, this is Leonard and Rajesh,
and you've already met Howard.
- It's nice to meet you.
- You too, as well also.
(Howard:)Yeah.
So how do you two know each other?
(Missy:)Oh, he once spent nine months
with my legs wrapped around his head.